Omid Hosseini

Tehran, Iran



omid.hosseini7@yahoo.com



(+98)9387227776



linkedin.com/in/omid-hosseini

Summary

Experienced Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in C#, ASP.NET (MVC/Core) and Microservices. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Software Engineering from the University of Applied Science and Technology.

Experience

№ Back-end Developer

AratelVC

May 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

- Back-end development (design and develop Daroopin restFul API).
- Back-end development (design and develop FinCore restFul API).

Full Stack Engineer

Negah-e Emrooz

2014 - Feb 2019 (5 years 2 months)

- Developed FAQ web application for Enbank.ir
- Developed web application for Issue Gift-Card (Micard Solution)
- Developed RMTO (Road Maintenance & Transportation Organization) web application for issuance permit to import goods
- Designed and developed Restful API for Jireyeketab (back-end)
- Designed and developed Jireyeketab android application (client)

Full Stack Developer

ShayganTadbirParsian May 2018 - Feb 2019 (10 months)

- Developed Sharjbook web application
- Developed Accounting web application

Full Stack Developer

Self Employed

Apr 2011 - Jun 2014 (3 years 3 months)

■ Manage, design and develop Lavasan.biz web application.

● Manage, design and develop LavasanDatabase android application.

Education

University of Applied Science and Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2014 - 2016



Islamic Azad University - Roudehen Branch

Associate's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2007 - 2010



Khaje nasir toosi

High School Diploma, Computer Science 2003 - 2006

Skills

C# • Asp.net core • ASP.NET MVC • Web Development • Software Development • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Microservices • Git • Agile Methodologies